Finding Aid for William Edward Beach photographs, 1931-1948
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photograph albums
  - Miscellaneous prints, 2 folders (Box 5)
Spring Mill
1337.
Leica 1086-1090 (Mill and old house)
Springport
Leica 744
Springville
Leica 1029-1030. (Tablet, old inn)
Squawfield
1462
Standish
192.
Leica Nos. 778 (Court House), 779-781 (Paul Bunyan)
Stanton
192
Sturgis
607
Tawas City
1075-1077
Tecumseh
13, 527.
Leica 49
Tekonsha
899
Thompson
1418
Three Oaks
649
Three Rivers
603, 1799, 2019
Traverse City
5-7, 1446, 1552-1553.
Leica Nos. 1313-1330 (logging wheels, engines, etc. Some markers)
Trenton
802.
Leica 525, 1339-1346 (Detroit Edison cars and building. Rotarians)
Troy
167-168
Unadilla
1399
Utica
Leica 430-432
Vermontville
1283.
Leica 560A, 992-994
Victoria
Leica 1240-1241
Walpole Island
474-476
Washtenaw County
354, 1079-1081
Waterloo
1461
Wayland
1976-1978
Wayne County
766
Wellston
1545-1557
West Branch
1303
White Cloud
Leica 772 (Court House)
White Pigeon
605, 1201
White Rock
910
Wisconsin (state of)
Leica 1229
Woodbury
1465
Wyandotte
175
Ypsilanti
71-72, 313, 366, 543, 1969.
Leica 61, 550 (Tablet), 1022 (Tablet, Chicago Road)
Subject Index, Kodak Series
Airports
236, 617, 2147, 2148, 2149
Animals
6, 114, 524, 850, 1253, 1472, 1535, 1592, 1957, 1966
Antiques and Historical Interest
493, 495, 496, 497, 498, 499, 500, 501, 502, 503, 504, 505, 506, 507, 508, 509, 510, 511, 541, 562, 620, 782, 798, 802, 805, 845, 1530, 1531, 1594, 1951, 1961
Arts and Crafts
1279, 1291, 1318 (Theater), 303 (Opera House), 353 (Music Hall), 1475 (Theater), 1476 (Theater), 1487 (Museum), 1491, 1527 (Museum)
Automobiles, Trucks, and Buses
49, 50, 52, 53, 67, 68, 73, 74, 75, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 94, 95, 219, 241, 259, 319, 320, 347, 460, 473, 103-104, 128, 154, 171, 492, 569, 575, 580, 581, 587, 738, 854, 855, 856, 871, 1094, 1100, 1101, 1276, 1470, 1471, 1495, 1496, 1661, 1692, 1794, 1800, 1969, 1971, 2028, 1978, 2143
Banners and Billboards
336, 286, 351, 2263, 2267
Barns
868, 869, 1089, 1241, 1267, 1804, 1810, 1811, 2065, 2150, 2151, 2153, 2154, 2160
Bridges
9, 10, 32, 66, 164, 173-174, 257, 283, 293, 327, 344, 365, 523, 537, 551, 1079, 1214, 1244, 1330, 1331, 1332, 1333, 1334, 1335, 1396, 1455, 1482, 1483, 1484, 1488, 1544, 1545, 1546, 1633, 2162, 2284, 2401, 2446
Businesses and Industries
throughout
Churches
14, 15, 20, 31, 54, 63, 129, 172, 294, 521, 527, 588, 594, 764, 861, 911, 1263, 1264, 1358, 1464, 1494, 1558, 1559, 1668, 1970, 2041, 2158, 2205, 2239, 2277, 2278
Courthouses
throughout
Fairs, Parades, and Bands
22, 209, 210, 250, 251, 340, 253, 256, 337, 436, 614, 630, 633, 634, 635, 637, 926, 930, 1217, 1218, 1219, 1220, 1221, 1222, 1228, 1230, 1967, 1968, 2054, 2055, 2056, 2215, 2216, 2217, 2218, 2219, 2221, 2425, 2426
Flags
271, 252, 636, 851, 1108
Gardens
7, 234
Gas Stations and Garages
36, 43, 45, 46, 77, 255, 266, 459, 491, 567, 852, 870, 874, 1120, 2204, 1250, 1309, 1269, 1274, 1295, 1311, 1314, 1329, 1400, 1473, 1542, 1976, 2018, 2027, 2144, 2146, 2192, 2193, 2202, 2235
Hotels and Taverns
480, 515, 519, 534, 640, 848, 863, 929, 1109, 1272, 1293, 1493, 2019, 2203, 2211
Houses
throughout
Indians
474, 475, 476, 526, 538, 539, 753, 766, 778
Lighthouses
3
Lumbering
1582, 1585, 1586, 1587, 1588, 1590, 1591, 1595, 1075, 1415, 1418, 1587, 1588, 1590, 2071, 2427, 2428
Machines
239, 244, 245, 246, 247, 248, 249, 872, 1090, 1197, 2183, 2195, 2196, 2197, 2225, 2226, 2227, 2228
Masons
72, 92, 98, 120, 127, 131, 155-156, 157, 162-163, 169, 176, 185, 195, 201, 207, 212, 217, 269, 304, 315, 316, 326
453, 533, 615, 616, 618, 619, 628, 629, 1202, 1206, 1359, 1425, 1440, 1669, 1670, 2212
Mills
202, 242, 310, 311, 317, 318, 443, 540, 834, 895 896, 897, 1084, 1085, 1110, 1207, 1208, 1246, 1280, 1281, 1286, 1292
1337, 1399, 1428, 1461, 1463, 1534, 1631, 2035, 2163, 2189, 2199, 2200, 2402, 2403
Nature Scenes
354, 517, 592, 743, 744, 767, 1095, 1431, 1436, 1481, 1543, 1547, 1565, 1803, 1805, 1806, 1807, 2058, 2059, 2060, 2073, 2145
Parks and Monuments
throughout
People
60, 220, 226, 254, 261, 267, 331, 338, 345, 338, 345, 355, 360, 447, 520, 559, 573, 728, 734, 742, 759, 761, 838, 849, 1102, 1103, 1105, 1107, 1265, 1307, 1402, 1460, 1469, 1474, 1662, 1663, 1792, 1965, 2113, 2114, 2115, 2117, 2170, 2171, 2220, 2229, 2252, 2265, 2266, 2424
Post Offices
59, 585, 598, 1215, 1216, 1304, 1401, 2000, 2166
Public Buildings, Miscellaneous
11 (Bank), 16 (Library), 30 (Hospital), 51 (Hospital), 56 (Jail), 62 (Capitol), 227 (Bank), 233 (Prison), 299 (Library), 330 (Bank), 451 (Hospital), 452 (Sanitarium), 525 (Library), 528 (Eastern Star), 568 (County Road Commission), 770 (Armory), 858 (Recreation Building), 859 (Recreation Building)
860 (Hospital), 928 (Town Hall), 1319, 1424, 1541, 1575 (City Hall), 1666 (Hospital), 1954 (Bank), 1962, 1994 (Bank), 2010 (Bank), 2012, 2022 (Capital), 2034 (Fire Hall), 2040 (Funeral Home), 2057 (Library), 2165 (Roller Rink), 2236 (Library), 2287 (Museum), 2288 (Museum), 2289 (Museum), 2404 (City News)
Railroads and Railroad Stations
58, 740, 836, 846, 1257, 1361, 2177, 2264, 2383, 2384, 2385, 2387, 2388, 2389, 2390, 2430
Rivers and Lakes
4, 203, 222, 223, 224, 343, 349, 512, 783, 484, 864, 865, 912, 913, 1076, 1078, 1080, 1081, 1086, 1096, 1245, 1282, 1327, 1328, 1635, 2283, 2285, 2287, 1087
Roads and Streets
295, 265, 225, 32, 1083, 1251, 1262, 1306, 1316, 1362, 1468, 1540, 2161, 2164, 2198
Schools and Colleges
17-18, 44, 93, 97, 193, 199, 216, 366, 307, 339, 565, 631, 763, 902, 903, 904, 905, 906
1252, 1422, 1449, 1450, 1490, 1996, 2032, 2033, 2206
Ships
10, 750, 1259, 1336, 1409, 1410
Subject Index, Leica Series
Animals
371, 372, 373, 432, 1196, 1197, 1198, 1199, 1200, 1201, 1301, 1318, 1319, 1320, 1321, 1322
Automobiles, Trucks, and Buses
64, 376, 377, 378, 379, 380, 438, 439, 538, 540, 559, 792, 1205, 1273, 1340, 1346
Bridges
27, 30, 49, 53, 54, 492, 525, 555, 594, 600, 605, 1000, 1005, 1006, 1070, 1096, 1065, 1247, 1263, 1300
Business and Industries
40, 41, 43, 44, 45, 72, 73, 83, 94, 93, 430, 431, 440, 446, 447, 448, 486, 507, 512, 513, 514, 560-6, 560-7 and 8, 560-11 and 12, 1043, 1051, 1214, 1342, 1343
Churches
7, 47, 48, 108, 445, 471, 487, 495, 496, 497, 498, 499, 500, 502, 503, 504, 554, 560-3, 591, 614, 743, 783, 993, 505
Courthouses
548, 589, 596, 737, 772, 775, 776, 777, 778, 785, 787, 1027, 1270
Fairs, Parades, and Bands
65, 387, 388, 389, 390, 391, 392, 560-4 and 5, 393, 394, 395, 396, 397, 398, 399, 400, 401, 402, 403, 404, 405, 406, 407, 408, 409, 410, 411, 452, 453, 456, 457, 458, 459, 460, 462, 462, 463, 584, 585, 586, 607, 608, 738, 1011, 1012, 1039, 1040, 1045, 1090, 1191, 1192, 1193 [see also Masons]
Gas Stations
15, 38, 470, 471, 511
Hotels and Taverns
310, 489, 527, 995, 1030, 1094, 1095
Houses
13, 42, 352, 529, 553, 560-9 and 10, 560-15, 619, 745, 749 (Log Cabin), 770, 791, 1037, 1050, 1056, 1057, 1088, 1332, 1334
Lighthouses
442, 1253, 1308
Machines
420, 421, 1058, 1271, 1272, 1279
Masons
78, 88, 581, 582, 580, 640, 641, 647, 649, 650, 651, 652, 653, 654, 655, 656, 657, 658, 659, 660, 661, 662, 663, 664, 665, 666, 667, 668, 669, 670, 671, 672, 673, 674, 675, 676, 677, 678, 679, 680, 681, 682, 683, 688, 689, 690, 691, 692, 693, 694, 695, 696, 697, 698, 699
701, 702, 703, 704, 705, 706, 708, 709, 710, 711, 712, 713, 714, 715, 716, 717, 718, 719, 720, 721, 722, 723, 724, 725, 726, 727, 728, 729, 730, 731, 732, 733, 734, 788, 1229
Mills
62, 63, 80, 11, 85, 429, 541, 572, 573, 576, 577, 1087, 1064, 1274
Nature Scenes
3, 5, 34, 35, 98, 349, 434, 435, 601, 604, 764, 1071, 1072, 1061, 1062, 1069, 1209, 1210, 1240, 1245, 1246, 1252, 1254, 1255, 1256, 1264, 1274, 1290, 1291, 1292, 1293, 1345
Parks and Monuments
throughout
People
4, 8, 9, 18, 19, 21, 32, 33, 39, 79, 81, 82, 95, 92, 418, 419, 433, 473, 474, 475, 476, 477, 494, 509, 510, 517, 518, 519, 520, 521, 542, 579, 590, 625, 629, 630, 634, 635, 769, 1035, 1036, 1041, 1042, 1048, 1049, 1076, 1341, 1344
Public Buildings, Miscellaneous
6 (Library), 37 (Theater), 417 (P.O.), 451 (Republican Headquarters), 465 (Hospital), 491 (Grange Hall), 516 (State Police Barrack), 763 (Odd Fellows Hall), 796, 797, 999 (Auditorium), 1003 (Radio Station), 1007, 1008, 1026 (Post Office), 1194, 1204, 1309, 1347
Railroads and Railroad Stations
74, 75, 14, 17, 28, 606, 1013, 1014, 1015, 1016, 1017, 1018, 1019, 1020, 1074, 1075, 1077, 1078, 1079, 1080, 1081, 1082, 1083, 1084, 1085, 1314, 1315, 1339
Rivers and Lakes
22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 29, 52, 72, 422, 423, 424, 425, 426, 427, 490, 535, 536, 537, 574, 593, 593, 603, 746, 747, 750, 793, 1052, 1053, 1054, 1055, 1066, 1067, 1086
Roads and Streets
59, 60, 449, 522, 561, 768, 771, 1068, 1230 (Crystal Falls), 1348 (Tunnel at Sarnia)
Schools and Colleges
31, 532, 533, 789, 1251, 1333
Ships
1004, 1009, 1010, 1217
Winans, Edwin B.
624-628